{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Third deck",
      "description": "got pine",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "birds",
      "description": "ducks",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "cakes",
      "description": "eat",
      "id": 7
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "third card",
      "back": "back",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "A tiny moss ball",
      "back": "Marimo",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "front",
      "back": "back",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "add me",
      "back": "back side",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "add me 222",
      "back": "back side 222",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "add me 3333",
      "back": "back 3333",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "1111",
      "back": "2222",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "555",
      "back": "55555",
      "deckIid": 2,
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "strawberry\nsponge\nwhipped cream",
      "back": "short cake",
      "deckIid": 7,
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 17
    }
  ]
}